Guide to the Toni Beauchamp Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Market Square Park Project, A Project of DiverseWorks, id165990
  - DiverseWorks, id166004
    - Funding, id166191
      - Contributions, 1995-1996; id166228 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Financials, id166192
      - Financials, 1989-1990; id166230 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Financials, 1991-1995; id166231 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
      - Financial Report, 1993-1995; id166232 (Box 12, Folder 5-7)
      - Laguna Art Museum, 1991-1992; id166233 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Various, 1989-1993; id166234 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, id166193
      - Development Correspondence, 1991-1992; id166236 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence Emily Todd, 1995; id166237 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence Alexander Gray, 1995; id166238 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Various Correspondence, 1986-2006; id166239 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Special Events, id166194
      - 10 Years Gala, 1993; id166242 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - UH School Musical Gala, 1991; id166243 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - 1996 Gala, id166244 (Box 12, Folder 16-19)
      - Miami Trip, 1997; id166245 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - 25th Anniversary, 2007; id166246 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Ads and Forms, 1995; id166247 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - John Hilliard – Press, 1992-1993; id166248 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Board Update on Market Square Park, 1987-1989; id166249 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - DiverseWorks Panel for the Last 30 Years, 1997; id166250 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Patron Group, 1991-1992; id166251 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Art Space Administration, 1989; id166252 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Various, 1986-2006; id166253 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
- Art Lies, id166254
  This series details another major project in this collection: Toni Beauchamp’s long-running affiliation with Art Lies magazine (now a part of Gulf Coast Magazine, a project of UH Creative Writing Program). The Series is further broken down into various subseries that deal with history, projects, correspondence, management, government relations, committees, financials, and articles, all in relation to Art Lies.
  - History, id166264
    - Strategic Planning, 2003-2006; id166281 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Governance, 1996-2006; id166282 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Goals, 2005-2006; id166283 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Art Lies Overview, undated; id166284 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Proposal, 2008; id166285 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Administration and Governance, 2005; id166286 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Vision Statement, 2006; id166287 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Development Plan, 2006; id166288 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Various, 2005; id166289 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Management, id166265
    - Membership, 2004-2005; id166291 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Membership Renewal, 2005; id166292 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Administrative, 2002-2003; id166293 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Membership and Organization Information, undated; id166294 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Anjali Gupta, undated; id166295 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Editorial, 2008; id166296 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Nominations, 2004-2005; id166297 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Surveys, 2004; id166298 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Staff Evaluation Guide, 2003; id166299 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Roster / Vote / Ref / Bio, 2001-2002; id166300 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, id166266
    - Roberta Smith, 2007; id166302 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - John Bryant, 2002-2003; id166303 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Underwriter, 2004-2005; id166304 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Chris French and Lauri Nelson, 2001-2004; id166305 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - James Bae, 2006; id166306 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Various, 2002-2008; id166307 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Personnel and Human Resources, id166267
    - Development Director Position Description, undated; id166309 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Tim Stanley, 2006; id166310 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Resumes, undated; id166311 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Executive Director Search, 2001-2008; id166312 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Various Job Descriptions, 2009; id166313 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Funding, id166268
    - Grant Requests– Foundations, 2001-2003; id166316 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Development Consultant, 2005; id166317 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Benefit Dinner, 2007; id166318 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Individual Contributions, 2001-2004; id166319 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Andy Warhol Request for Funding, 2005-2006; id166320 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Grant Requests– Governance, 2005; id166321 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Grant Request Closures, 2002; id166322 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Fred Foundation Funding, 2001-2007; id166323 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - CACHH Grant for Art Lies, 2002; id166324 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Board Contributions, 2002-2005; id166325 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Art Lies Benefit Dinner, 2006; id166326 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Grant Request, 2006; id166327 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Floppy Disc Containing Foundation Letters and Attachment, 2002; id166328 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, id166269
    - Annual Board Retreat, 2006-2007; id166330 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Minutes, 2004-2007; id166331 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Orientation, 2002; id166332 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Strategic Planning, 2006; id166333 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Meetings, 2001-2002; id166334 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Meetings, 2003-2005; id166335 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Meetings, 2007-2008; id166336 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Meetings Agendas, 2006-2007; id166337 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Various, 2002-2009; id166338 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Toni's Personal Notes, id166270
    - Committee Notes, 2005; id166340 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Meeting Notes, 2001-2002; id166341 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, undated; id166342 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Financials, id166271
    - Budget, 2002-2009; id166344 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer Report, 2007-2008; id166345 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Various, undated; id166346 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials, id166272
    - Ref / Competition, 2001-2004; id166348 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Various, 2007-2010; id166349 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Art Lies Works, id166273
    - Critiquing Residency Program, 2005-2006; id166351 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Art Criticism Reference, 2005; id166352 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Organizations Affiliated with Art Lies, id166274
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston Harris (CACHH), 2002-2003; id166354 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - CAM,H Trustee, 2003; id166355 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Houston Endowment, 2001-2005; id166356 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Professional Consultant, id166275
    - Production and Distribution Masterpiece Litho Incorporated, 2003; id166358 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Networking and Publicity, id166276
    - Invitation Cards and Thank-You Notes, 2003-2005; id166360 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Fresh Arts Coalition Thank-You Letter, 2006; id166361 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Art Lies Distribution Notebook or Journal, 2006; id166362 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Subscriber Campaign, 2001-2002; id166363 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Newsletter / Website Ideas, 2005-2006; id166364 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Marketing / Development, 2002-2003; id166365 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Advertising Information and Issues List, 2005; id166366 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Various Emails, 2006; id166367 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Special Events, id166277
    - Rice Design Alliance Reception, 2006; id166370 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Benefit Dinner Lecture Series, 2006; id166371 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Chinati Foundations Members Dinner, 2005; id166372 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Distinguished Lecture Series, 2006-2007; id166373 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Gala, 2007; id166374 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - INDIKA Dinner, 2007; id166375 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - CAM,H Development Workshop, 2005; id166376 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 10th Anniversary, 2004; id166377 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - An Urbane Evening, 2005; id166378 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Various, 2004-2009; id166379 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Federal Agencies, id166278
    - NEA, 2002; id166381 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Insurance, id166279
    - DDO Insurance, 2003-2004; id166383 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- good, Toni’s Millennium Project, 2000-2001; id166255
  This series represents the fourth major project detailed in this collection. It consists of various elements of good, the book that Toni edited and produced in recognition of the new century: her Millennium Project. She commissioned artist Mel Chin to produce a sculpture (subsequently gifted to MFA,H) and cover art, and local people from all walks of life to write their story of being in Houston; edited the resulting essays; and produced the book. The Series is further broken down into various subseries that deal with history, projects, correspondence, management, Government relations, committees, financials, and articles relating to good.
  - good Project Materials, id169608
    - good, 1999; id166385 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Millennium Card, 2000; id166386 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Millennium Celebration, 1997-1999; id166387 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Momentum, 1999; id166388 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Copyrights, 2000; id166389 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Core Design, 2000; id166390 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Interview / Speech, 2000-2001; id166391 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Response to Book, 2001; id166392 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - A Proposed Legacy for the Millennium Project, 2000; id166393 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Toni’s Foreword, 2000; id166394 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Maps, 2000; id166395 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Millennium in Progress, 2000; id166396 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Expenses, 1999-2001; id166397 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Biographies / References Not Used, 2000; id166398 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Poly Koch, 2000; id166399 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Research Materials Used in Putting Together good, id166400
    - Various Correspondence, 2007; id166407 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Various Biographies, 2000; id166408 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Various Printouts, 2000; id166409 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Various, 1999-2000; id166410 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Essayists, id166401
    - Lois Stark, 2000; id166443 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Anne Mendelsohn, 2000; id166444 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Sehba Sarwar, 2000; id166445 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Jim Harithas, 2000; id166446 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Sarah Cortez, 2000; id166447 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Suzanne Theis, 2000; id166448 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Kevin Shanley, 2000; id166449 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Gwendolyn Scott, 2000; id166450 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Dr. Frank Borreca, 2000; id166451 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Karl Kilian, 2000; id166452 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Jenna Terry, 2000; id166453 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Cynthia Macdonald, 2000; id166454 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - William Steen, 2000; id166455 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Russell Contreras, 2000; id166456 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Lorenzo Thomas, 2000; id166457 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Stephen Klineberg, 2000; id166458 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Carlos Jimenez, 2000; id166459 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Stephen Fox, 2000; id166460 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Bob Eury, 2000; id166461 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Susie Kalil, 2000; id166462 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Walter Hopps, 2000; id166463 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Diana Davila Martinez, 2000; id166464 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Andrea Chin, 2000; id166465 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Pokey Anderson, 2000; id166466 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Bao-Long Chu, 2000; id166467 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Melanie Lawson, 2000; id166468 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Patsy Cravens, 2000; id166469 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Mel Chin--Correspondence / Essay, 2000; id166470 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Various Potential Essayists, 2000; id166471 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Various Essays, 2000; id166472 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Blaffer Gallery, University of Houston, id166256
  This series represents the fifth major project detailed in this collection. It consists of various projects and events with which Toni Beauchamp was affiliated in relation to Blaffer Gallery, University of Houston. This Series is further broken down into subseries that deal with projects, correspondence, management, and articles relating to the Blaffer.
  - Various University of Houston, id169609
    - Contributions, 1991-2005; id166475 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - U of H Art Dept. / Michelle Taylor, undated; id166476 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Alumni, 1984-1995; id166477 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Partners in Philanthropy, University of Houston School of Music, 1991; id166478 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Various, undated; id166479 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Booklet, undated; id166480 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Blaffer Gallery, id166481
    - The Houston Exhibition, 2000; id166483 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Toni and Jeff Beauchamp Correspondence, 1988-2003; id166484 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee, 1981-1982; id166485 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Board, 1982-1985; id166486 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Various, 1978-1995; id166487 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Friends of Integrative Medicine (FIM), The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center., id166257
  This series documents the sixth major project in this collection. Toni conceived, founded, and led FIM until her death in 2012, after which it continued as a project of UTMDACC. The Series consists of various projects and events with which Toni Beauchamp was affiliated in relation to Friends of Integrative Medicine. This Series is further broken down into subseries that deal with projects, correspondence, management, and articles relating to FIM.
  - Integrative and holistic medical files, id169610
    - Strategic Planning, 2009; id166490 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - FIM Booklet, 2008-2009; id166491 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Lecture Series, 2009-2011; id166492 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Cohen Talk, 2009; id166493 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Campaign to Transform Cancer Care, 2009; id166494 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Whole Health MD, 2008; id166495 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Access Booklet– N. O’Connor, 2007; id166496 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Mind Body, 2007-2008; id166497 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Medical Systems, 2008; id166498 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - FIM@ MDACC, undated; id166499 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Spirituality and Healing in Medicine– The Harvard Medical School and the Mind / Body Etc., 1995; id166500 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - FIM 50I(c)(3), 2008-2009; id166501 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Packets, 2008-2009; id166502 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - FIM Current Meetings, 2008-2009; id166503 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Files, 2011; id166504 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - To Distribute to Members, 2008; id166505 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Event Notes / Meeting Minutes, 2011; id166506 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Take to MAREA, undated; id166507 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence Toni Beauchamp, 2001-2011; id166508 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - FIM Membership, 2009; id166509 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Solicitation Letters, 2008-2009; id166510 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Toni’s Personal Notes, undated; id166511 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Various, 2008-2009; id166512 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Publications, id166513
    - Place of Wellness UTMDACC Publications, 2007-2010; id166516 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Messenger Magazine, 2009-2011; id166517 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Network Magazine, 2008-2009; id166518 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Integrative: A Clinical Journal, 2009; id166519 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Alternative Therapies, 2010; id166520 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Self-Healing Magazine, 2004-2007; id166521 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Various Magazines, undated; id166522 (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
  - Articles/Printouts, id166514
    - Stress-Reduction and Energy-Based Articles, 2008-2009; id166524 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - New York Times / World Reports, 2008-2009; id166525 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Various Printouts, undated; id166526 (Box 17, Folder 13-16)
    - Various Printouts with Personal Notes, undated; id166527 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
- Uncommon Cents, id166258
  This series represents the seventh major project in this collection. It consists of various projects and events with which Toni Beauchamp was affiliated in relation to Uncommon Cents, an investment “club” that Toni co-conceived, co-founded, and led. This Series is further broken down into subseries that deal with projects, correspondence, management, and articles relating to Common Cents.
  - Uncommon Cents Dissolution, 2005; id166529 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Treasurer’s Duties, 1999-2002; id166530 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Women of Achievement Investment Club– Treasurers Ref Book, 2002; id166531 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Monthly Reports, 2003-2005; id166532 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Investment Club Reports, 1998; id166533 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Financial Transactions, undated; id166534 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee and Action Items, 2000; id166535 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Rosters, 1997-2002; id166536 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Various, 2005; id166537 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Other Works, id166259
  This series documents various other projects Toni Beauchamp was affiliated with in Houston’s Art Community/Organizations and her other varied interests. This series is further broken down into subseries that are characterized by the names of these other groups, including Cultural Arts Council of Houston/ Harris County; Museum of Fine Arts, Houston; Contemporary Art Museum Houston, and Orange Show; as well as arts advocacy.
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston/Harris County, id166538
    - History, id166578
      - By-Laws / Policy, 1998; id166594 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Strategic Planning, undated; id166595 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Transition Plan, 1998; id166596 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - An Agency Plan for the CACHH, 1994; id166597 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Organizational Analysis, 1998; id166598 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - General, 2001; id166599 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - The CACHH Book, 1984-1986; id166600 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
      - Draft of Three Year Plan, 1985-1986; id166601 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
      - Overview / Background Booklet, undated; id166602 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Management, id166579
      - Human Resource Policy and Procedures, 1994; id166605 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Agency Profile / Programs, 1999; id166606 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - General Candidates Information, 1998; id166607 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Constituent Input, 1998-1999; id166608 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Removal CAP, 1999; id166609 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Three Issues Two, 1998; id166610 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Management Assistant and Organizational Development Enterprise, 2001; id166611 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Working Drafts, 1995-1998; id166612 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Survey and Evaluation, 1998-1999; id166613 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - CACHH vs. Theatre District, 1996; id166614 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Policies and Procedures, 1985-1986; id166615 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - : Fellowship Program, 1984-1986; id166616 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - The Long-Range Plan, 1986; id166617 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Public Affairs Law, 1985-1986; id166618 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Board– General Information, 1983-1985; id166619 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Affiliated Organizations, id166580
      - Cultural Tourism, 1998; id166621 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Houston Coalition for Visual Arts (HCVA), 1998; id166622 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Museum District, 1997-2000; id166623 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Memorandums, id166581
      - Marion McCollam, 1997-1998; id166625 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Lucy Dabney, 1999; id166626 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - John Walsh, 1998-1999; id166627 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Bill Hill, 1997-1998; id166628 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Local Government, id166582
      - Cultural Plan for Houston and Harris County, 1992; id166630 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - County Government, undated; id166631 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - City Government, 1997-1998; id166632 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Events and Conferences, id166583
      - Arts Day, 1990-1994; id166634 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - NCNB Conference Washington DC, 1999; id166635 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Committees, id166584
      - Long Range Planning, 1985-1986; id166638 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Public Service Sports, 1982-1984; id166639 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Nominating Committee, 1984-1986; id166640 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Steering Committee, 1985-1987; id166641 (Box 19, Folder 19-20)
      - Nominating and Steering Committee, 1986-1987; id166643 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Executive Director Search, 1998-1999; id166644 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Executive Director Search, 1998-1999; id166645 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
      - Strategic Planning, 1997-2001; id166646 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Civic andArt Design, 1997-1998; id166647 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Allocations Review Committee, 1996-1997; id166648 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Civic Art Ordinance, 1999-2000; id166649 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Search Committee Survey, 1999; id166650 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Search Committee Meeting Note, 1999; id166651 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Projects, id166585
      - Civic Art: Urban Design, 1997-1998; id166653 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Houston Frame Work “Public Art”, 1996; id166654 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors, id166586
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 1999; id166657 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
      - Board of Directors Manual, 1994-1999; id166658 (Box 20, Folder 13-17)
      - Board Development Proposal, 1998; id166659 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Board Roster Information, 1997-2000; id166660 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Non Profit Board Ref, 1997-1999; id166661 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Board of Director Rosters, 1992-2000; id166662 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Directory, 1982-1984; id166663 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Meetings, 1984-1985; id166664 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987; id166665 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Retreat, 1986; id166666 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Financials / Funding, id166587
      - Fiscal Report to Mayor and Council, 1998; id166669 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Report on Audit of Financial Statements, 1999-2001; id166670 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Checks, 1998; id166671 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - HOT Allocation FYE, 2000; id166672 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Annual Reports / Financial Statements, 1983-1986; id166673 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Development Donor List, undated; id166674 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Grant Awards, 1999; id166675 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-1997; id166676 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Articles/Notes/Publications, id166588
      - News Releases, 1986-1994; id166678 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Toni’s Personal Notes / Magazines, 1998-1999; id166679 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Artwork, undated; id166680 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Various Articles, undated; id166681 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Career Development Opportunities/Candidates, id166589
      - Eleanor Fink, 1997-1999; id166684 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Resumes, 1999; id166685 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - MCA, 1998-1999; id166686 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Job Profile– Executive Director, 1999; id166687 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Alberto Rafols, 1999; id166688 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Janet Spitz, 1999; id166689 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Pedro Rodriguez, 1999; id166690 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Mark Toubin, 1999; id166691 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Leilani Duke, 1999; id166692 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Executive Director, 1998; id166693 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Mike Bisesi, 1999; id166694 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Cissy Segall, 1999; id166695 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Victor Kendall, 1998-1999; id166696 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Patricia Jones, 1999; id166697 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Ted Eliatas, 1999; id166698 (Box 21, Folder 31)